

BARBARA ABONG

barbarajona62@gmail.com 306-580-8614

ABOUT ME

I am a critical thinker and a focused Computer Information Technology student with two years of experience in troubleshooting and documenting problems. I also have over 3 years experience in interacting with clients and making sure their needs are met.

REFERENCE

Rudy Mihalicz (supervisor at Access Communications)-1-866-363-2225

EXPERIENCE

Client Support ● St Therese Villa ● August 2021 – Nov 2022

- Daily one on one room visits with residents and help them fix any technical difficulties.
- Help set up video calls and facilitate communication between residents and their families

Quality Assurance Rep • Access Communications • Sep 2020 – July 2021

- Performing quality tests, performance surveys and making sure clients are receiving quality service.
- Creating reports documenting errors and how the errors were resolved.

EDUCATION

Computer Information Technology Diploma • Lethbridge College • 2021 - 2023

High School Diploma • CPC Bali • 2014- 2016

SKILLS

- Excellent communication, customer service and interpersonal skills.
- Creative and innovative
- Analytical and problem-solving abilities.